Description
    The file is designed to enable the BigInteger class to be used in C++ as basic data types. Since the class is calculated on the basis of the vector<int> class, it computes much slower than int, but it also gets higher precision.

Overloaded operator
Type				Operator
Binary operator			+, -, *, /, %
Relational operators		==, !=, <, >, <=, >=
Logical   operators		||, &&, !
Unary operator			+, -
Self-added/Decrement operator	++, --
Assignment   operator		=, +=, -=, *=, /=, %=
Bitwise				>>, <<

Other functions			Supported
Function name			Function
size_t size() const		Return digits of BigInteger object
BigInteger e(size_t n) const	Return BigInteger Object multiplied by 10^n
BigInteger abs() const		Return absolute value of BigInteger Object

    More functions are available on the basis of existing code.

    Limitation of the class:
    1. It can perform an implicit type conversion with bool, int and long long(only from low precision to high precision) numbers. But can't do this with float numbers
    2. The input format defaults to continuous numbers, no other characters, and no formatting checks on the input
    3. Divide by 0 error without processing